This is number three of three [music] of
my favorite e-ink devices. This is a
really small e-reader. But, the beauty
of this device is that it's small enough
to be able to stick on the back of your
phone, and it [music] even has a magnet
in it. So, you can kind of carry it
around like that. It's kind of
unrealistic to bring like both my phone
and an e-reader. It's it becomes way too
bulky in my pockets. [music]
And so, this kind of fills that gap
where you can easily carry this out. It
can easily [music] fit in any of your
pockets, and it even sticks to the back
of your phone. And it's really just a
folder that you can drag and drop books
[music] onto to read books on this.
Using this kind of makes me nostalgic
for my iPhone Mini because it kind of
has that similar form factor, and it
reminds me [music] that this is the
ideal form factor of a phone.